威尔 · 森特斯: 这就是我们令人惊异的原型性质的工作是紫色的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That was our amazing
prototypal nature of jobs are those purple
代码，JavaScript 的原型本质。
lines, the prototypal
nature of JavaScript.
这是一个非常美好的方式来确保我们不会
That's a very beautiful way
of ensuring that we don't
必须在用户1、用户2和用户500上直接增量。
have to have increment directly on
user 1 and user 2 and user 500.
但是我们可以访问它，因为当我们没有在垫子上找到增量时
But we have access to it because when
we don't find increment on the mat
在对象本身上，JavaScript 不会恐慌。
on the object itself
JavaScript doesn't panic.
它看起来是1中的原型属性，指向它链接到用户函数的地方
It looks it is proto property in 1, heads
up to where it links to user function
存储并找到该函数的一个保存的版本，抓取它并使用它。
store and finds a single saved version
of that function, grabs it, and uses it.
我们喜欢它。
We love it.
但正如我所说的，它确实涉及到相当多的代码编写。
But as I say, it does involve quite
a little bit of writing of code.
所以如果我们回头看，我们使用 object.create 手动创建对象,
So if we look back, we had creating
the object manually using object.create,
存储在一个新用户中。
storing in a new user.
顺便说一下，这只是一个暂时的名字，他们从来不用这个名字。
By the way, just a temporary name for
it,they never get stuck with that name.
手动返回该对象后，我们还编写了相应的代码。
Returning out that object manually,
we wrote the code for that as well.
创建一个使用函数存储的键。
Creating a bond to use a function store.
如果我们可以自动化这些东西不是很好吗？
Wouldn't it be nice if we
could automate that stuff?
你知道吗？
And you know what?
会有一个关键词，我会用蓝色，但是
There's gonna be a key word,
I'm gonna use blue for it, but
我要插入在运行我的函数之前，那个关键字是什么？
I'm gonna insert in front of running my
function, what is that keyword everybody?
因为我已经写了，我不应该有，这是什么？
Cuz I've written up already I
shouldn't have, what is it?
布莱登: 新的。
&gt;&gt; Braden: New.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 新的，干得好，各位。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: New,
well done everybody.
对不起，新的[声音] ，为什么如果我们说它是一个新的,
Sorry, new [SOUND], and
why if we say it's a new,
有趣的是，我要说这个词和
interesting, I'm going
to say that word and
人们，它将自动化，这么多东西为我们。
people it's going to automate so
much stuff for us.
它会在这里自动创建一个对象。
It's going to create automatically
inside of here an object.
所以所有蓝色的东西都是要做的东西
So everything in blue is going to be
the stuff that's going to be done for
通过新的关键词。
us by the new keyword.
所以我们不需要这样做，我们不需要再编写代码了。
So we don't have to do it,
we don't have to write that code anymore.
它会自动为我们创建一个新对象。
It's gonna create a new object for
us automatically.
它会自动为我们返回那个物体。
It's gonna return that object out for
us automatically.
是啊,
Yeah,
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这也是，相信它或者
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's also, believe it or
不，它会使链接到某些对象充满了功能在这里,
not, it's gonna make the link to some
object full of functions out here,
对我们来说也是自动的。
automatically for us, as well.
也会自动为我们设置原型属性。
Gonna set the proto property
automatically for us as well.
我要说的是，我们可能会想到的地方？
I will say this, to where we might think?
因为，等等，在我们手动设置寻找新用户的对象之前
Because, hold on, before we manually set
that object that we sought a new user to
有它隐藏原型财产链接使用功能商店已经存在。
have it hidden proto property linked to
use a function store was already there.
但是现在我认为情况就是这样。
But now I thought would be the case.
所以我不知道我们要把我们的共享存储功能放在哪里，如果没有的话
So I don't know where we're going to
put our shared store functions if not
在用户功能存储中，我们不能再自己控制了。
in user function store, we're not
going to control any more ourselves.
另一个问题是，我是如何在这个对象上添加属性的？
Another thing by the way is, how did I
get to put properties on this object?
为了能够访问这个对象，我映射了哪个标签
What label did I have mapped in order
to be able to access this object and
粘在上面。
stick properties on it.
我给它贴了什么标签？
What label did I give it?
布莱登: 新用户。
&gt;&gt; Braden: New user.
如果这个对象是为我们自动创建的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: If that object is
being automatically created for us,
我能给它贴上标签吗？
do I get to assign it a label?
没有。
No.
我们有几个问题，链接到哪里？
So we got a couple of questions,
where we gonna link off to?
这个对象会自动给出什么标签？
And what's this object gonna
automatically given as a label?
我希望这不是我们用来
I hope it's not the same
label as we have for
其他函数调用中的其他函数，那就有点傻了，不是吗？
something else in other function calls,
that'd be a bit silly, wouldn't it?
是的，我们不想，我们不想让它被说，例如,
Yeah, we wouldn't wanna, we wouldn't
want to have it be say for example,
这个在另一个地方指的是完全不同的东西。
this that in another place refers
to something totally different.
那太疯狂了。
That would be very crazy.
好了，好了，同志们，新的关键词自动化了艰苦的工作。
All right, okay, people, so
new keyword automates the hard work.
当我们调用返回对象的函数时,
When we call the function
that returns an object,
有了新的关键词，我们可以自动完成两件事。
with the new keyword in
front we automate 2 things.
首先，我们自动创建对象。
Well, firstly,
we create the object automatically.
然后，我们看到我已经把新的在它前面。
Then, so we see I've put
the new in front of it now.
然后我们自动返回对象。
Then we return the object automatically.
与此同时，我们要确保把东西放进去。
In the meantime,
we make sure we stick stuff in it.
但是现在我们需要调整如何写这个函数的函数体，userCreator,
But we now need to adjust how we write
the body of this function, userCreator,
它的密码。
the code of it.
我们如何引用这个自动创建的对象和
How can we refer to this
auto-created object and
知道把我们的单一版本，共享函数的一个版本放在哪里吗？
know where to put our single versions,
one of versions of the shared functions?
因为我没有选择把它放进什么东西里
Because I didn't get to
choose to put it in something
叫做用户功能存储。
called user function store anymore.
我们现在可以回答的第一个问题是，猜一猜。
The first bit we can answer right now,
have a guess.
你认为他们把这个自动创建任何人的对象叫什么
What do you think they call this object
that automatically created anyone take
猜猜看，彼得？
a guess, Peter?
布莱登: 是的，威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的,
&gt;&gt; Braden: Yes
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes,
这就是我们要说的。
this exactly is going to be called this.
因为这指的是它唯一给定的对象或者
Given that this refers to
its only given object or
那个物体的另一个阶段。
a different stage of that object.
然后，当我们稍后在对象及其执行角落运行 increment 时,
Then when we later on run increment on
the object and in its execution corner,
它指的是点左边的物体,
is that this refers to whatever
the object is to the left of the dot,
他们是完全分开的。
they're totally separate.
当我们阅读我们的代码时，这有点令人困惑,
That's a little bit confusing
when we read our code, well,
不是一点点，而是非常令人困惑。
not just a little bit,
it's profoundly confusing.
这是另一个关键的规则。
This is the other key
rule of how this works.
它总是点左边的对象，当我们运行一个方法时,
It's always whatever the object is to
the left of the dot when we run a method,
这是隐式分配给用户1的。
that this is implicitly
assigned to the user 1.
如果我们使用一个新的关键字，它还有另一个角色，即自动创建的对象
It has one other role, if we use a new
keyword, the automatically created object
都会标记这个，但它们是完全独立的。
inside of that execution context is gonna
label this, but they're totally separate.
我们要在哪里输出我们想要的单个保存的函数版本,
Okay, where are we gonna put out single
saved version of the function we want,
所有执行过程中产生的对象？
all objects that come from executing?
这些都是完全不同的用户创建执行，我们希望在哪里
These are totally different executions
of user creator, where do we want all
那些共享的功能，这些对象有一个链接来存储？
those shared functions that these
objects have a link to to be stored?
为了理解这一点，我们需要再加上一段精彩的插曲,
To understand that, we need to add
one more preeminent interlude,
让我们看看。
let's have a look.
在我们开始之前,
Preeminent interlude, before we do that,
新的关键字让我们的许多手工工作自动化了。
the new keyword automates
a lot of our manual work.
你看，我们摆脱了对象的创建，就要完成了
You see we get rid of the creation of
the object is going to be done for
给我们新钥匙。
us with the new key.
当我们运行用户创建的新是要插入和
When we run user created
new is gonna insert and
它会自动把这条线固定在那里,
it's going to automatically
stick that line up there,
创建一个新的对象将尝试这样做，而不是新用户。
creating a new object is going to
try to do this not to new user.
然后我们就可以用这个访问那个物体了。
We're then gonna have access
to that object using this.
我们不再使用 newUser.name 了。
We're not gonna do newUser.name anymore.
我们要用这个名字来修理它。
We're gonna do this name
to fix stuff in it.
它会自动将这个对象返回给用户1。
And it's gonna automatically return
that this object out into user 1.
但是我们的功能存储，我们与功能存储的连接已经结束了。
But our function store, our connection to
function store that's done and gone now.
那么我们要去哪里呢？
So where are we going to?
我们需要一个大的古老的物体，我们可以肯定，在他们的帮助下,
We need a big old object that we
can be sure that with their help,
使用新的关键字，自动创建的对象,
with a new keyword, the object
that gets automatically created,
它的原始属性会连接到某个对象。
its proto property will
link off to some object.
我需要知道它会在哪里。
I need to know where that's gonna be.
为了找出它会在哪里，让我们来看看这个小插曲。
To find out where it's gonna be, let's
take a look at this little interlude.
函数在 JavaScript 中既是对象又是函数。
Functions are both objects and
functions in JavaScript.
伙计们，我们需要它。
We need it over here, people.
这里有一小段额外的插曲，对我们来说真的很重要。
A little bit of a bonus interlude here,
really important for us to understand.
所以我们有，记忆，你知道它只是一个,
So we have, memory, you know it's just a,
让我们做一个，威尔 · 森塔斯: 一点工作。
let's do a,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Bit of work.
是啊，看看这是基于
Yeah, look at that was based on
我们的一位观众的建议。
advice from one of our audience.
这里的第一行，丹，我们在内存中做什么？
So line 1 here, Dan,
what are we doing in memory?
丹: 我们存储的是 multiplyBy2函数。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We are storing
the function multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，存储倍增2函数，就是这个。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, store
the function multiplyBy2, there it is.
好的，2号线，杰夫，我们在那条线上做什么？
Okay, line 2 Jeff,
what are we doing in that line?
杰夫: 我们正在 multilyby2上创建一个物业商店,
&gt;&gt; Jeff: We are creating
a property store on multiplyBy2,
威尔 · 桑坦斯: 但它是一个函数,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But it's a function,
除非是杰夫？
unless Jeff?
杰夫: 是一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: It's an object.
一个函数加一个对象。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A function
plus an object.
一旦 JavaScript 看到这个关键字函数,
It turns out as soon as that
JavaScript sees that keyword function,
知道函数即将到来,
knows a function is coming,
我们得到一个函数加，威尔 · 森坦斯: a
we get a function plus,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A big
旧物附着。
old object attached.
如果我们在函数的末尾使用括号，我们马上就会看到。
If we use parens on the end of
the function, well, we’ll see in a second.
如果我们在函数标签的末尾使用点，则
If we use dot on the end of
the function label, the label for
这个函数，我们可以接触到 Jeff 的哪一部分？
the function,
which bit do we get access to Jeff?
杰夫: 那是什么？
&gt;&gt; Jeff: What’s that?
如果我们在多个 by2标签的末尾使用点,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: If we use dot on
the end of the multiplyBy2 label,
函数对象组合的哪一部分。
which bit of the function object combo.
我叫他们，我们有哪一部分？
I call them, which bit do we have?
我们得到对象位的访问权，正好通过点，进入它。
We get access to the object bit, exactly
right through the dot, into it we go.
我们要在里面放什么，布莱登？
And what are we gonna store in it, Braden?
布莱登: 5。
&gt;&gt; Braden: 5.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，什么地产的名称？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
on what property name?
存储。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Stored.
威尔 · 森特斯: 存储，看看这个，太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Stored,
look at that, fantastic.
但也许看看下一行,
But maybe, look at that next line,
也许当我们运行 multimyby2，输入3。
maybe when we then run
multiplyBy2 with the input of 3.
也许这样做不再有效，因为这样做可能会覆盖函数
Maybe that doesn't work anymore because
maybe doing this overwrote the function
暗号，是吗，布莱登？
code, did it Braden?
不，是什么让我们现在仍然使用函数位,
No, what allows us now to
still use the function bit,
我们用的是什么符号？
what symbols we're using here?
布莱登: 巴黎人。
&gt;&gt; Braden: The parens.
威尔 · 森坦斯: parenns，意思是去使用函数位,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Parens, and
that means go use the function bit,
它会返回6。
it's gonna return out 6.
但是，也许使用函数会覆盖对象。
But maybe that using the function
is overwritten the object, maybe.
如果我们使用点符号，我们还能访问我们的对象吗？
Braden do we still get access to our
object if we use a dot notation?
布莱登: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Yes.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我们知道。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, we do.
函数对象，我们说的是对象，但是
Function object and
we're talking about an object as much, but
它在每个功能中都有。
it is in every function is there.
但结果会非常非常非常有用。
But it's gonna turn out here to be super,
super, super useful.
但是如果你想相信所有的功能也有,
But if you want to believe
will all functions also have,
非常好的现场什么所有的函数也默认有。
very nice spot what all
functions also have by default.
原型？
&gt;&gt; Braden: Prototype?
威尔 · 森塔斯: a，我不想这么说。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A,
I don't wanna say that.
一个财产，不，好吧，是的，那是什么，但是，不，好吧，是的，他们做，天哪，是的。
A property, no well, yeah, that's what,
but a, no, well, yes they do, gosh, yeah.
我们将会看到这一点，尽管你会在 OOP 大厅中看到暂停。
We're gonna see that,
though you'll see that in OOP hall pause.
专门研究 OOP haber，但是现在对我们来说更重要的是，它们有一个属性。
Specialize OOP Habert, but more important
to us right now, they have a property.
没什么神奇的当你看到 doc 原型的时候,
Nothing magical,
when you see the doc prototype,
我们认为，也许这其中有某种神奇的意外收获。
we think, maybe there's some kind
of magical bonus in all that.
它是一个物体的属性，这个属性的名字是什么？
It's a property of an object and
the name of the property is what Braden?
2.
&gt;&gt; Braden: MultiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不完全是，彼得，房子的名字是？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Not quite, Peter,
the name of the property is?
原型。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Prototype.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Prototype.
没错，这个性质只是原型和 o。
Exactly, that property
is just prototype and o.
这就是有趣的地方。
Here is where it gets interesting.
所有对象格式的函数都会自动启用
It's always on that all functions in
their object format automatically have
他们的财产。
a property on them.
我的意思是，为什么点点，实际上是自动在那里,
I mean, why did the dot dot dot,
actually was that automatically there,
整个原型？
whole prototype?
它不是隐藏的财产。
It is not a hidden property.
就像是对象位的一个属性。
It's like a it's a property
on the object bit.
我们只是不想看到这一点。
We just don't tend to look at this bit.
我们需要控制台日志多次按下一点下来。
We'd need to console log multiple
by to press a little down.
我的意思是，我猜那些东西是对我们隐藏起来的，而且就在那里。
I mean, I guess the objects kind of
hidden from us and it's on there.
这是什么？
What is it?
丹，默认的原型属性是什么？
Dan, what is the prototype
property default to be?
空物体。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Empty object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个又大又旧的空物体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A big old empty object.
看看这个。
Look at that.
意思是，我们要使用的函数，当它得到执行和
Meaning, the function that we're gonna
use new one when it gets executed and
它会自动创建一个迫切需要链接的对象,
it creates an object automatically that
desperately needs a place to link to,
一个旧的大空对象，在其中存储我们的函数与我们一起存储函数。
an old big empty object, in which to store
our functions with us to store functions.
这个函数不仅仅是一个函数，它还是一个什么杰夫？
That function is not just a function,
it's also a what Jeff?
杰夫: 一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: An object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个客体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: An object.
那个物体不是空的，里面有什么？
And that object is not empty,
it's got what in that?
杰夫: 一个原型财产。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: A prototype property.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 一个正确的原型，说得好，那是什么，马克？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A prototype properly,
nicely put, which is what, Mark?
马特: 一个又大又旧的空物体。
&gt;&gt; Matt: A big old empty object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们认为在哪些地方，人们可能会觉得它有意义
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Where do we think
folk that it might make sense for
我们得到了新的关键字
us to have the new keyword or for
决定了新的关键字自动创建对象
JavaScript to have decided the new
keywords auto created object inside
创建一个函数，让它拥有自己的协议
the running of the userCreate
a function for it to have its protocol
如果它不能指定它的用户函数存储，那么连接是什么呢？
connection be to if it can't specify
that its user function store?
马特，你觉得在哪里说得通？
Matt, where do you think
it might make sense?
马特: 原型属性。
&gt;&gt; Matt: The prototype property.
Will Sentance: 我们将要运行的函数的 Prototype 属性
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Prototype property of
the function that we're then going to run
新的关键字，或者我们要运行新的关键字，这样它创建
the new keyword or we're going to run with
the new keyword on such that it creates
里面有个自动物体。
an automatic object inside.
它的原始属性
And that's gonna have a bond for
its proto property to
那个原型属性，也就是一个物体。
that prototype property,
which is an object.
协议不会链接使用函数存储，但是
The protocol is going to not link
to use the function store, but
连接到这个对象。
link up to this object.
因此，我们最好把我们的函数，我们希望所有的对象出来
So we better put our functions that
we want all objects that come out of
自动，或出来运行用户创建的新关键字在前面
the auto, or come out to running user
created with the new keyword in front that
自动创建一个对象，它需要有一个链接的地方
creates an object automatically, which
needs somewhere to have a link to for
它的共同功能。
its shared functions.
它们自动成为创建对象的函数
They're automatically gonna be that
function that creates the object with
对象版本中新关键字的帮助,
the help of the new keyword
in its object version,
在它的原型属性中，它本身就是一个对象。
in the prototype property of it,
which is itself An object.